Jeff Gold Collection ARC.0037
Library and Archives
Jeff Gold Collection
1938-2010, undated
ARC.0037
Library and Archives
35.33 Linear feet (14 records cartons, 3 Hollinger boxes, 3 oversize boxes, 1 audiovisual box, 1 card box, 4 flat file drawers)
The Jeff Gold Collection contains a variety of material that document numerous artists and people in the music industry from the late 1950s through 2010, and includes some undated items. The collection is organized into six series by format, topic, or source; including artist files, subject files, posters, 16 Magazine, audiovisual materials, and items from the collections of Art Collins and Ralph Gleason. Please note that files may contain only one item about an artist or subject, such as a press release or photograph.
Collins, Art, 1953-2005
Gleason, Ralph J.
Related Archival Materials
Related materials providing content on Art Collins may be found in the following collections in this repository: Art Collins Papers.
Separated Materials
Books, periodicals, and commercial audiovisual materials have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Jeff Gold Collection" in the library catalog for a list of donated items. If you are unable to find what you are looking for, consult the Library and Archives staff to ensure these materials are available.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Patrons must sign the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights statement on the Researcher Registration form before using this collection. The condition of the audiovisual materials in this collection has not yet been determined for playback purposes. Some of the audiovisual materials in the collection are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
Accruals
Accruals are interfiled within the collection.
Biographical Note
Jeff Gold is a collector of rock and roll memorabilia who operates the Internet-based store Recordmecca. Rolling Stone magazine called him one of the top five collectors of music memorabilia in the world, and he acts as a consultant for various cultural institutions, including the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and the Experience Music Project.
Sources
"About Recordmecca." Recordmecca. Accessed July 28, 2011. 2011. http://www.recordmecca.com/content_page.aspx?id=2.
Custodial History
The Jeff Gold Collection was received by the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Museum, Inc. as several gifts from Jeff Gold over the course of 2001-2010.
Beatles.; Bowie, David; Dylan, Bob, 1941-; Gold, Jeff, 1956-; Hendrix, Jimi; Jefferson Airplane (Musical group); Pop, Iggy, 1947-; Red Hot Chili Peppers (Musical group); Rolling Stones; Simon and Garfunkel; T. Rex (Musical group); Uttal, Jody; Who (Musical group); 1/4-inch audiotapes; 16 magazine; 3/4-inch videocassettes; Audiocassettes; Concert tours; Contracts; Fan clubs; Hi-8; Music journalists--United States.; Music trade--Management.; Photographs; Postcards; Posters; Press kits; Printed ephemera; Psychedelic rock music--California--San Francisco.; Rock groups--United States.; Rock music--England; VHS (TM); Video tapes; Videocassettes
- Series I: Artist Files, 1957-2004, undated
  Scope and Contents
  Series I: Artist Files contains a wide array of documents pertaining to popular musicians and rock groups from the 1950s through 2004. The documents include contracts, photographs, press releases, programs, and sheet music. Many of the files contain only one item, which in most cases is described as a general note. Files that are located in Museum storage are currently stored off-site. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Aerosmith, 1984-1989, undated (Box AF1, Folder 1)
    Museum Accession Numbers
    A2002.82.123, A2002.82.31-A2002.82.33, A2002.82.137-A2002.82.139, A2002.82.166-A2002.82.170
  - The Allman Brothers, undated (Box AF1, Folder 2)
  - Arnaz, Desi, Jr., undated (Box AF6, Folder 1)
    Museum Accession Number
    A2004.54.24
  - The Association, 1967 (Box AF1, Folder 3)
    A2002.82.60
  - Bad Company, 1976 (Box AF6, Folder 2)
    A2004.54.95, A2004.54.110, A2004.54.251
    Separated Materials
    Items in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - The Band, 1979, 1996 (Box AF1, Folder 4)
  - The Beach Boys
    - General, 1969-1975, undated (Box AF1, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, 1970 November-circa 1971 (Box AF1, Folder 5)
      General note
      Three color snapshots and two black-and-white prints.
      A2002.82.34-A2002.82.36, A2004.54.62-A2004.54.63
  - The Beatles
    - General
      - "All You Need Is Ringo" article, 1970 Feb. 8 (Box OS1, Folder 1, Object 1)
        two page feature in West (Los Angeles Times)
      - Color pinup album magazine, 1964 (Box AF1, Folder 6)
      - A Hard Day's Night advertising book, 1964 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 1)
        A2002.82.90
      - Memo regarding appearance on "Juke Box Jury", 1963 Dec. 10 (Box AF1, Folder 7)
        A2004.54.61
      - Press kit for CD release of Help!, Rubber Soul, and Revolver, 1987 (Box AF1, Folder 7)
        A2004.54.50a-A2004.54.50b
      - Press kit for 20th anniversary release of Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band, 1987 (Box AF1, Folder 7)
        A2004.54.128a-A2004.54.128c
      - Promotional materials, 1964, 2000 (Box AF1, Folder 7)
      - Tokyo Fan Club magazine, issue 8, 1994 (Box AF1, Folder 8)
      - Trading cards, undated (Box AF5)
      - U.S. Tour programs, 1964 (Box OS1, Folder 1, Object 2-3)
        A2005.105.40-A2005.105.41
        Two copies in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
    - Photographic Material
      - Early prints and negatives, 1960-1962 (Box AF1, Folder 9)
        prints made at a later date
      - Snapshots from a concert in Milan, Italy, 1965 (Box AF1, Folder 10)
        copies made from original prints, includes letter of explanation, 2006
      - Black-and-white print of Beatles wearing Sergeant Pepper costumes, 1967 (Box AF1, Folder 9)
        A2004.54.129
      - Oversize, circa 1963-1965 (Object Museum storage)
        A2003.27.1-A2003.27.3
        Materials in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Beck, Jeff, undated (Box AF1, Folder 11)
  - Berry, Chuck, 1971, undated (Box AF1, Folder 12)
    A2002.82.21, A2002.82.29
  - Black Sabbath, circa 1978 (Box AF1, Folder 13)
    A2002.82.178
  - Bloodrock, 1970 (Box AF1, Folder 14)
  - The Blues Brothers, undated (Box AF1, Folder 15)
  - Bonzo Dog Band, undated (Box OS1, Folder 1)
  - Bow Wow Wow, undated (Box AF1, Folder 16)
  - Bowie, David
    - General
      - Album art proofs, 1976 (Object Museum storage)
        A2001.93.29a-A2001.93.29c
      - Merry Christmas, Mr. Lawrence press packet, undated (Box AF1, Folder 19)
      - Newspaper clippings, posters, and other materials, 1971-1976 (Box AF3, Folder 52-54, Box OS1, Folder 1, Box OS2)
      - Press kit for Isolar LP, 1976 (Box AF1, Folder 17)
        A2004.54.56a-A2004.54.56b
      - Promotional materials, 1977-1983, 1995 (Box AF1, Folder 17)
      - Publications, 1976, 1983 (Box AF1, Folder 18)
        A2002.82.179
      - Stage '78 tour program, 1978 (Box AF1, Folder 17)
        A2004.54.103
    - Photographs, 1978-1985, undated (Box AF1, Folder 20)
      Includes publicity photographs and an image of Bowie with Mick Jagger at the China Club, New York City.
      A2004.54.33
  - Brides of Funkenstein, undated (Box AF1, Folder 21)
  - Brown, James
    - Flyer, 1983 (Box AF1, Folder 22)
      A2002.82.14
    - James Brown Admiration Society documents, 1965-1967 (Box AF1, Folder 22)
      August 1965 newsletter on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
      A2004.54.88-A2004.54.95
  - Buckley, Tim, 1967, 1972-1974, undated (Box AF1, Folder 23)
    Includes oversize photograph.
    Oversize photograph, A2005.105.32
    Oversize photograph in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Burdon, Eric, 1967, 1970 (Box AF6, Folder 3)
    A2004.54.111-A2004.54.113b
  - The Byrds
    - Photocopy of book chapter, undated (Box AF1, Folder 24)
    - Photographs, circa 1968 (Box AF1, Folder 24)
      A2004.54.30a-A2004.54.30c
  - Can, undated (Box AF1, Folder 25)
  - Captain Beefheart, 1970, 1972 (Box AF1, Folder 26, Box OS1, Folder 2)
  - The Carpenters
    - "For All We Know" sheet music, 1970 (Box AF1, Folder 27)
      A2002.82.59
    - Photograph, undated (Box AF1, Folder 27)
      A2004.54.36
      Item in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
    - Brown paper bags, undated (Box OS1, Folder 2)
  - Chambers, Kasey, 2001 (Box AF1, Folder 28)
  - Charles, Ray, 1965, undated (Box AF1, Folder 29)
  - Clark, Gene, undated (Box AF1, Folder 30)
  - Cochise, 1971 (Box OS1, Folder 2)
  - Cooke, Sam, 1959 (Box AF1, Folder 31)
    color photocopies of a signed contract with the William Morris agency
  - Cooder, Ry
    - Press kit for Boomer's Story, undated (Box AF6, Folder 4)
      A2004.54.7a-A2004.54.7b
    - Boomer's Story album cover art, 1972 (Box OS3, Folder 1, Object 7)
      A2005.105.34
  - Costello, Elvis, circa 1979, undated (Box AF1, Folder 32)
  - Country Joe & the Fish, 1968 (Box AF1, Folder 33)
    A2004.54.81
    multiple copies of a fan club certificate
  - Crosby, Stills, Nash and Young, 1969-1970, 2000 (Box AF1, Folder 34)
    A2002.82.81
  - The Cure, 1987 (Box AF1, Folder 35)
  - Damn Yankees, 1991 (Box AF1, Folder 36)
  - Dave Clark Five
    - Fan club items, 1966, undated (Box AF1, Folder 37)
      A2002.82.192-A2002.82.193
    - Fave magazine questionnaire for Rick Huxley, undated (Box AF1, Folder 37)
      A2004.54.23
    - Press kit, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 2)
  - DEVO, 1978, 1981 (Box AF1, Folder 38)
  - Dio, Ronnie James, 1983 (Box AF1, Folder 39)
    A2002.82.174
  - Domino, Fats, undated (Box AF1, Folder 40)
  - Donegan, Lonnie, 1956 (Box AF1, Folder 41)
    A2002.82.173
  - The Doors
    - General, 1969, undated (Box AF1, Folder 42)
    - Negatives, undated (Box AF1, Folder 43)
  - Dylan, Bob, 1975, 1977, undated (Box AF1, Folder 44-45, Box OS1, Folder 2)
  - The Eagles, circa 1994, 2008 (Box AF1, Folder 46-47, Box OS2, Folder 2)
  - Ellis, Shirley, undated (Box AF1, Folder 48)
  - Emerson, Lake & Palmer, circa 1972, 1977, undated (Box AF1, Folder 49)
  - Eno, Brian, circa 1970s (Box AF1, Folder 50)
    A2002.82.182
  - The Everly Brothers, 1983, undated (Box AF1, Folder 51)
    A2002.82.184
  - Fairport Convention, 1968, undated (Box AF1, Folder 52)
  - Family, 1969, undated (Box AF1, Folder 53, Box OS1, Folder 3)
  - Fitzgerald, Ella, 1968, undated (Box AF1, Folder 54)
  - Fleetwood Mac
    - Peter Green-era materials, 1971, undated (Box AF1, Folder 55)
    - Behind the Mask tour itinerary, 1990 (Box AF6, Folder 5)
      A2004.54.125
  - Flying Burrito Brothers
    - Gilded Palace of Sin label copy, 1969 February 4 (Box OS1, Folder 3)
    - Lyrics, undated (Object Museum storage)
      A2001.80.24-A2001.80.25
    - Press kit, undated (Box AF1, Folder 56)
      A2002.82.47a-A2002.82.47b
  - Fogerty, John, 1997 (Box AF4, Folder 1)
  - Franklin, Aretha, 1964, 1969 (Box AF1, Folder 57)
    A2002.82.50, A2002.82.112
  - The Fugs, undated (Box AF1, Folder 58)
    A2002.82.80
  - Gabriel, Peter, 1977-1984 (Box AF1, Folder 59)
  - Garcia, Jerry, 1983, 1987 (Box AF1, Folder 60)
    Flyer for the Jerry Garcia Band and two copies of a playbill.
    A2004.54.86, A2004.54.223
  - Genesis, circa 1970 (Box AF1, Folder 61)
  - Geronimo Black, undated (Box AF1, Folder 62)
  - Goffin, David and King, Carole, 1959-1960 (Box AF1, Folder 63)
    Gerry Goffin and Carole King
  - Goo Goo Dolls, 1996-2000 (Box AF4, Folder 2-4)
  - The Grateful Dead, 1991 (Box AF1, Folder 64)
    Spring and summer tour itinerary.
    A2004.54.52, A2004.54.53
  - The Grateful Dead Blues for Allah album slick, 1975 (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-5, Object 2)
    A2004.54.199
  - Green, Al, 1978 (Box AF6, Folder 6)
    A2004.54.114a-A2004.54.114e
  - Green, Peter, 1970 (Box AF2, Folder 1)
  - Grimes, Howard, undated (Box AF2, Folder 2)
  - The Guess Who, undated (Box AF2, Folder 3)
  - Guthrie, Woody, circa 1963, 1967 (Box AF2, Folder 4)
    A2002.82.49, A2004.54.12, A2004.54.102
  - Haley, Bill, undated (Box AF6, Folder 7)
    A2004.54.1
  - Hardin, Tim, undated (Box AF2, Folder 5)
  - Harley, Steve (and Cockney Rebel), circa 1976 (Box AF2, Folder 6)
  - Harrison, George, circa 1971, 1974 (Box AF2, Folder 7)
  - Hendrix, Jimi
    - Rainbow Bridge documents and photographs, 1972, undated (Box AF2, Folder 9)
      A2004.54.40-A2004.54.42
    - Oversize
      - Rainbow Bridge album cover proof, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 3-5)
      - The Cry of Love LP cover art, 1970 (Object Museum storage)
      - Advertisement for Electric Ladyland, undated (Box OS1, Folder 3, Object 2)
    - General, 1969, 1975, circa 1999 (Box AF2, Folder 8)
      Primarily consists of materials from The Jimi Hendrix Exhibition: Guitar Player magazine, invitation to release party for Live at the Fillmore East LP, press release for Crash Landing LP, newspaper advertisement for Devonshire Downs festival.
      A2004.54.27, A2004.54.59, A2004.54.72, A2005.105.44
      Newspaper advertisement in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Herman's Hermits, undated (Box AF2, Folder 10)
    Press kit for Tiger Beat, handwritten note from Peter Noone to 16 Magazine
    A2002.82.148a-A2002.82.148i, A2004.54.26, A2004.54.38-A2004.54.39
    Note from Peter Noone on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
  - Howlin' Wolf, 1966, 1972 (Box AF2, Folder 11)
    one newspaper clipping, and a photocopy of The London Howlin' Wolf Sessions LP cover
  - Humble Pie, undated (Box AF2, Folder 12)
    one photograph
  - Hutto, J.B. (and the New Hawks), 1979-1980 (Box AF2, Folder 13)
  - Isley Brothers, 1959 (Box AF2, Folder 14)
    contains copyright forms and lead sheets for Shout, Nobody But Me
  - J. Geils Band, circa 1970-1971 (Box AF2, Folder 15)
  - Jackson 5, 1971 September, undated (Box AF2, Folder 16)
    Creem magazine and photograph.
    A2004.54.87, A2002.82.115
  - Jackson, Janet, 1989 (Box AF6, Folder 8)
    A2004.54.80a-A2004.54.80b
  - Jackson, Michael, undated (Box AF2, Folder 16)
    A2002.82.121, A2002.82.129, A2002.82.130
  - Jagger, Mick
    - General, 1986 (Box AF2, Folder 17)
      Running Out of Luck press kit, The Nightingale press kit, and postage stamps.
      A2002.82.30a-A2002.82.30h, A2004.54.2
    - Photographs, undated (Box AF2, Folder 17)
  - Jefferson Airplane, undated (Box AF2, Folder 18)
  - Jethro Tull, 1971 (Box AF2, Folder 19)
    three copies of a flyer for show at Ohio State University, Columbus, OH
  - John, Elton, 1966-1992, undated (Box AF2, Folder 20)
    contains photographs, one contract, and a press kit
    A2002.82.37-A2002.82.39, A2002.82.61-A2002.82.78, A2002.82.133-A2002.82.136, A2002.82.162-A2002.82.164
  - John, Little Willie, 1959, 1964 (Box AF2, Folder 21)
  - Jones, Quincy. Mellow Madness album cover art, undated (Object Museum storage)
    A2005.105.8, A2005.105.111
  - Joplin, Janis, 1968, 1969 May 26, 1970 October 5 (Box AF2, Folder 22)
    A2002.82.119, A2004.54.21
    Columbia Records press kit, Newsweek magazine, and newspaper clipping on Joplin's death.
    Separated Materials note
    Newsweek magazine on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
  - Jordan, Louis, 1973 (Box AF6, Folder 9)
    A2004.54.19
  - King, B.B., undated (Box AF2, Folder 23)
    A2002.82.18
  - King Crimson, 1971-1974, undated (Box AF2, Folder 24)
    Includes Agora flyer and invoices.
  - The Kinks, 1970, circa 1975, undated (Box AF2, Folder 25)
    Includes Schoolboys in Disgrace stamps, Lola Versus Powerman and the Moneygoround LP label copy, and Something Else album cover art.
    A2002.82.181, A2005.105.29
    Something Else album cover art in Museum storage. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society album art, c. 1968 (Box OS3, Folder 1, Object 6a-b)
  - lang, k.d., 1996-2001 (Box AF4, Folder 5-7)
    tour itinerary books
  - The Leaves, 1966 (Box AF6, Folder 10)
    A2004.54.132a-A2004.54.132b
  - Led Zeppelin
    - General, 1975 (Box AF2, Folder 26)
      includes program for concert at Earl's Court
    - Photographs, 1971-1973, undated (Box AF2, Folder 27)
  - Lee, Brenda, 1961 (Box AF2, Folder 28)
    contains one British concert program
  - The Lemon Pipers, 1967 (Box AF2, Folder 29)
    A2002.82.152
  - Lennon, John
    - General, 1969-1982 (Box AF2, Folder 30)
      Includes photographs and a playbill for the 1982 off-Broadway musical Lennon.
    - Newspaper clippings from death, 1980 (Box AF2, Folder 31)
    - Press kit for This is not here art show (Everson Museum of Art, Syracuse, NY), circa 1970s (Drawer-folder FF.3.2-5, Object 1)
      A2004.54.204a-A2004.54.204b
      Item on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
  - Lewis, Jerry Lee, 1957-1966 (Box AF2, Folder 32)
    A2002.82.79, A2002.82.100a-A2002.82.100i, A2002.82.140-A2002.82.141
  - Little Anthony and the Imperials, 1965 (Box AF2, Folder 33)
    contains one contract
    A2002.82.124
  - Little Richard, 1975 (Box AF2, Folder 34)
    contains one photograph
    A2002.82.101
  - MC5, undated (Box AF2, Folder 35)
    A2002.82.113
  - Madonna, 1996, undated (Box AF2, Folder 36, Box OS1, Folder 3)
    Includes Sex pamphlets from Warner Books Inc.
    A2002.82.208a-A2002.82.208e, A2004.54.104-A2004.54.105
  - Mandel, Harvey, 1972 (Box AF2, Folder 37)
    A2002.82.158
    One contract.
  - Marley, Bob, 1978 (Box AF2, Folder 38)
    contains two copies of 1978 tour program
    A2002.82.200-A2002.82.201
  - Mayall, John, 1970 (Box AF2, Folder 39)
    contains one press kit
  - McCartney, Paul
    - Greeting card with datebook, 1976 (Box AF6, Folder 11)
      A2004.54.49a-A2004.54.49b
    - North American tour press kit, 1989 (Box AF2, Folder 40)
      A2004.54.133a-A2004.54.133h
    - Photographs, undated (Box AF2, Folder 40, Box OS1, Folder 3)
    - Calendar with photographs by Linda McCartney, 1981 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 6)
  - McLean, Don, 1974 (Box AF2, Folder 41)
  - The Monkees, 1967 (Box AF2, Folder 42)
    A2002.82.20
  - Monroe, Bill, 1963 (Box AF2, Folder 43)
    contains one application for the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, and one Columbia Records ad
  - Moore, Gerald, undated (Box AF2, Folder 44)
    Reggae Guitars; contains one newspaper clipping from World Pop News
  - Morrison, Jim, undated (Box OS1, Folder 3, Box AF2, Folder 45)
    contains three photographs, including one of grave site
    A2002.82.51-A2002.82.52
  - Mott the Hoople, 1969-1974 (Box AF2, Folder 46)
    A2002.82.175a-A2002.82.175f
    includes press kit, tour program, and photocopied lead sheets
  - The Move, undated (Box AF2, Folder 47)
    contains one advertisement
  - Neil, Fred, undated (Box AF6, Folder 12)
    A2004.54.28a-A2004.54.28b
  - New York Dolls, 1973-1974 (Box AF2, Folder 48)
    press kit
    "The New York Dolls Fact Sheet" on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
  - Newman, Randy, undated (Object Museum storage)
    Includes self-titled first album cover proof.
    A2005.105.33
  - Nice and Nasty 3, 2003, undated (Box AF2, Folder 49)
    contains flyers for early hip-hop shows, with authentication forms
  - Nico, undated (Box AF2, Folder 50)
  - Nilsson, Harry, undated (Box AF2, Folder 51)
    contains one page of typed lyrics to Daddy's Song
  - Ono, Yoko, undated (Box AF2, Folder 52)
    includes one pamphlet for Approximately Infinite Universe LP
  - Parker, Junior, 1957 (Box AF2, Folder 53)
  - Peel, David (and the lower east side), undated (Box AF2, Folder 54)
    multiple copies of a promotional flyer
    A2002.82.102-A2002.82.105
  - Peter, Paul and Mary, undated (Box AF6, Folder 13)
    A2004.54.32
  - Petty, Tom (and the Heartbreakers), 1977, 1995, 1999 (Box AF2, Folder 55)
    contains two tour itinerary books, and one press book
  - Pink Floyd, 1967, circa 1973 (Box AF2, Folder 56)
    Includes Zigzag, Vol. 3 no. 8, and a handbill for first New York performance.
    A2002.82.19, A2004.54.57
  - Pop, Iggy, 1986, 2005, undated (Box AF2, Folder 57, Object Museum storage, Box OS1, Folder 4)
    Includes oversize photograph with David Bowie.
    A2005.105.39
  - Presley, Elvis, 1957, 1977 (Box AF2, Folder 58)
    includes photographs
    A2002.82.117-A2002.82.118
  - Procol Harum, 1967, 1973, circa 1975 (Box AF2, Folder 59)
  - Public Image Limited, 1984 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 7)
    Includes This Is What You Want, This Is What You Get album cover proof.
    A2005.105.6
  - Queen, 1977-1978 (Box OS1, Folder 4, Box AF2, Folder 60)
    tour programs
  - R.E.M., 1985-1987, 1995, undated (Box AF2, Folder 61)
    Includes '95 tourbook, autographed photograph, and tour programs for Work, Pageantry, and Reconstruction.
    A2004.54.100, A2004.54.121-A2004.54.123
  - The Ramones
    - General, 1976, 1981, undated (Box AF2, Folder 62)
      A2004.54.10, A2004.54.73, A2004.54.74, A2004.54.76
      Includes flyer for show at The Bottom Line, Sire Records promotional photograph, Punk magazine, Vol. 1 no. 3, and Rock 'n Roll High School promotional item.
    - Postcards
      - Fan club promotion, undated (Box AF2, Folder 62)
        A2004.54.75
      - Leave Home LP promo, 1977 (Box AF2, Folder 62)
        A2004.54.77
      - Show at the Roxy, Los Angeles, with the Flaming Groovies, 1976 (Box AF2, Folder 62)
        A2004.54.78
  - The Rascals, undated (Box AF2, Folder 63)
    Contains one press kit.
    A2002.82.116a-A2002.82.116b
  - Red Hot Chili Peppers
    - Tour books, 1992-2004 (Box AF4, Folder 14-20)
    - Tour documents, 1999-2004 (Box AF4, Folder 9-13)
  - The Red Krayola, undated (Box AF2, Folder 64)
  - Redding, Otis, 1968 March, undated (Box AF2, Folder 65)
    Includes Blues and Soul Monthly magazine and press releases.
    A2004.54.51
  - Reed, Lou, 1974-1975 (Box AF2, Folder 66)
    contains two clippings
  - The Rolling Stones
    - Art work
      - Emotional Rescue album cover proofs, undated (Object Museum storage, Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 8-18)
        A2005.105.38
      - Sucking In the Seventies album cover proof, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 19-20)
      - Tattoo You album cover proof, undated (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 21)
      - "Undercover of the Night" ad art, 1983 (Drawer-folder FF.3.1-4, Object 22)
    - General, 1966-1985, undated
      - 1978 tour itinerary (Box AF2, Folder 67, Object 10)
        A2002.82.48
      - The Rolling Stones Discover America (Box AF2, Folder 67, Object 11)
        A2002.82.53
      - Gimme Shelter (film) press release, 1970 (Box AF2, Folder 67, Object 12)
        A2004.54.5a-A2004.54.5b
    - Photographs, 1965-1985, undated (Box OS1, Folder 4, Box AF2, Folder 69)
    - Programs, 1972-1976
      - European tour program, 1976 (Box AF2, Folder 68, Object 12)
        A2002.82.198